<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <!-- PAD File Version -->
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>

  <!-- Company Info -->
  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>AEDTP WORLD</Company_Name>
    <Address>Volta Region, Ghana</Address>
    <Country>Ghana</Country>
    <Email>aedtpworld@gmail.com</Email>
    <Website_URL>https://aedtpworld.codedesign.app</Website_URL>
    <Website_Info_URL>https://aedtpworld.neocities.org/</Website_Info_URL>
  </Company_Info>

  <!-- Program Info -->
  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>CHEMOLAB</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>1.0</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Date>2025-09-21</Program_Release_Date>
    <Program_Type>Application</Program_Type>
    <Program_Category>Educational</Program_Category>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Cost_Other>Freeware</Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Description>
      CHEMOLAB by AEDTP WORLD is a free offline educational chemistry app designed 
      for students, teachers, and self-learners. It organizes chemistry into 
      Categories, Topics, Subtopics, Solutions, Questions, and Answers with a 
      clean multi-page HTML interface. Users can explore Biochemistry, Organic 
      Chemistry, Inorganic Chemistry, Physical Chemistry, and Pure Chemistry 
      with interactive self-test questions and step-by-step solutions.

      Features include:
      • Organized by categories and alphabetic topic menus
      • Explanations of core concepts (buffers, pH, neutralization, stoichiometry, etc.)
      • Detailed study notes on Amino Acids, Proteins, Enzymes, Periodic Table, and more
      • Self-test questions with answers to reinforce learning
      • Clean card-style design with hover effects
      • Works fully offline in any modern web browser
      • Freeware – no cost, no internet required

      CHEMOLAB is ideal for classroom use, revision, and independent study. 
      It is developed and maintained by AEDTP WORLD, Ghana, as part of their 
      mission to create accessible educational software and creative tools.
    </Program_Description>

    <Program_Tags>
      Chemolab, AEDTP WORLD, Chemistry App, Educational Software, Offline Learning, 
      Student Resource, Classroom Tool, Study Aid, Biochemistry, Organic Chemistry, 
      Inorganic Chemistry, Physical Chemistry, Pure Chemistry, Chemistry Topics, 
      Chemistry Subtopics, Chemistry Questions, Chemistry Answers, Chemistry Solutions, 
      Buffers, pH Calculations, Neutralization, Amino Acids, Proteins, Enzymes, Alkanes, 
      Alkenes, Alcohols, Periodic Table, Coordination Compounds, Stoichiometry, 
      Buffer Solutions, Henderson Hasselbalch, Buffer Capacity, Science Education, 
      Ghana EdTech, Freeware Chemistry Software
    </Program_Tags>
  </Program_Info>

  <!-- Program Links -->
  <Program_Links>
    <Program_Icon_File_URL>
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/chemolab.png
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/chemolab.ico
    </Program_Icon_File_URL>
    <Program_Screenshot_URL>
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot1.jpg
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot2.png
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot3.png
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot4.jpg
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot5.png
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot6.jpg
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot7.jpg
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot8.jpg
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/screenshot9.jpg
    </Program_Screenshot_URL>
    <Program_Download_URL>
      https://archive.org/download/chemolabapp/chemolab.exe
      https://archive.org/download/chemolabapp/chemolab.zip
    </Program_Download_URL>
    <Program_Info_URL>
      https://aedtpworld.github.io/apps/chemolab/
    </Program_Info_URL>
  </Program_Links>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>

